<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- App Info -->
    <string name="app_name">BrightBuds</string>
    <string name="app_logo">BrightBuds Logo</string>

    <!-- Common -->
    <string name="parent_mode">Parent Dashboard</string>
    <string name="child_mode">Child Learning</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="reports">Reports</string>
    <string name="sync_now">Sync Now</string>
    <string name="learning_progress">Learning Progress</string>
    <string name="child_profile">Child Profile</string>
    <string name="last_synced">Last Synced:</string>
    <string name="music_enabled">Music Enabled</string>
    <string name="sound_effects">Sound Effects</string>
    <string name="content_desc_background">Background</string>
    <string name="content_desc_home">Home Button</string>
    <string name="content_desc_close">Close Button</string>


    <!-- accessibility label for a locked module icon -->
    <string name="locked_icon">Locked</string>


    <!-- Parent Dashboard -->
    <string name="parent_dashboard">Parent Dashboard</string>
    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="add_child">Add Child</string>
    <string name="generate_reports">Generate Reports</string>

    <!--Feed Monster Game -->
    <string name="target_number">Target number</string>
    <string name="monster_image">Monster</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>






    <!-- Child Profile -->
    <string name="save_child_button_text">Save Child Profile</string>
    <string name="saving_button_text">Saving...</string>

    <string name="terms_and_conditions_title">Terms &amp; Conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_content">
    <![CDATA[
    <h2>BrightBuds – Terms and Conditions</h2>

    <p><strong>Last Updated:</strong> November 2025</p>

    <h3>1. Purpose of the App</h3>
    <p>BrightBuds is an educational mobile application designed for early childhood learning. It combines songs, interactive games, and progress tracking tools to support literacy and numeracy development in children aged 2 to 6.</p>

    <h3>2. Parental Responsibility and Consent</h3>
    <ul>
        <li>Only verified parents or guardians may create and manage child profiles.</li>
        <li>Parental consent is required before any child information is created or stored.</li>
        <li>Parents are responsible for monitoring their child’s activities and securing their devices.</li>

    </ul>

    <h3>3. Privacy and Data Protection</h3>
    <ul>
        <li>BrightBuds complies with COPPA and follows strict data-minimisation practices.</li>
        <li>Personal data (child names, photos, words) is encrypted locally using AES-256.</li>
        <li>Only anonymised learning metrics are synced to Firebase for reporting.</li>
        <li>Parents may review or delete their child’s data at any time from the dashboard.</li>
        <li>No advertising, third-party tracking, or data selling occurs in BrightBuds.</li>
    </ul>

    <h3>4. Offline and Online Use</h3>
    <p>All modules work offline using local SQLite storage. When internet connectivity is restored, data automatically synchronises with Firebase using timestamp-based conflict resolution to ensure consistency.</p>

    <h3>5. Security Measures</h3>
    <ul>
        <li>All network communication is protected with HTTPS/TLS encryption.</li>
        <li>Database integrity is enforced through unique identifiers and foreign-key constraints.</li>
        <li>Administrative actions are logged and auditable.</li>
        <li>Backups and recovery snapshots prevent data loss or corruption.</li>
    </ul>

    <h3>6. Accessibility and Inclusivity</h3>
    <ul>
        <li>The interface follows WCAG accessibility standards with clear icons and high-contrast colors.</li>
        <li>Voice prompts support children who are not yet readers or have learning differences.</li>
        <li>Parents may customise modules with family photos or local language content.</li>
    </ul>

    <h3>7. Acceptable Use</h3>
    <p>Users agree to use BrightBuds solely for educational and non-commercial purposes, not to modify or distribute the application’s content, and to report any bugs or security issues responsibly.</p>

    <h3>8. Content and Intellectual Property</h3>
    <p>All learning materials, games, graphics, and songs are the intellectual property of the BrightBuds Team. Unauthorised reproduction or redistribution is prohibited.</p>

    <h3>9. Data Retention and Deletion</h3>
    <ul>
        <li>Data is retained only while the parent account is active.</li>
        <li>Deleting a child profile removes associated progress data permanently.</li>
        <li>Backup data is automatically purged within 30 days of deletion.</li>
    </ul>

    <h3>10. Limitation of Liability</h3>
    <p>BrightBuds is provided “as is” for educational use. The developers are not responsible for data loss, misuse, or device issues resulting from user error or unauthorised modification.</p>

    <h3>11. Updates to These Terms</h3>
    <p>These Terms and Conditions may be updated periodically to reflect legal or feature changes. Parents will be notified of significant updates through the Parent Dashboard.</p>

    <h3>12. Contact Information</h3>
    <p>For support or privacy enquiries, contact us at <strong>info@BrightMinds.com</strong>.</p>
    ]]>
</string>

</resources>
